{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312496979","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312496979"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" aeb08e25-f333-4320-82f0-543edc3ed78c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_V-F-E"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312515102","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312515102"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" aeb08e25-f333-4320-82f0-543edc3ed78c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_F-CH-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312541628","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312541628"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" aeb08e25-f333-4320-82f0-543edc3ed78c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_F-G-D"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312546607","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312546607"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" aeb08e25-f333-4320-82f0-543edc3ed78c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_CH-F-K"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312551398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312551398"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" aeb08e25-f333-4320-82f0-543edc3ed78c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_F-U-J"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312554587","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312554587"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" aeb08e25-f333-4320-82f0-543edc3ed78c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_L-F-Z"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312560577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312560577"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" aeb08e25-f333-4320-82f0-543edc3ed78c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_F-A-D"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312566081","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312566081"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" aeb08e25-f333-4320-82f0-543edc3ed78c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_R-N-F"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312571550","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312571550"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" aeb08e25-f333-4320-82f0-543edc3ed78c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_P-O-F"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312577961","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312577961"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" aeb08e25-f333-4320-82f0-543edc3ed78c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-B"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312583706","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312583705"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" aeb08e25-f333-4320-82f0-543edc3ed78c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-B"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312594961","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312594960"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312595559","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312595559"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312596225","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312596225"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312596380","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312596379"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312596773","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312596772"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312597193","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312597192"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312598314","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312598314"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312599322","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312599322"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" TUKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312599903","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312599903"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312600068","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312600068"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312600901","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312600901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312603672","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312603671"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312604701","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312604701"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312605736","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312605736"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312606801","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312606800"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIENDESHWA"," userResponse":" IKIENDESHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312608035","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312608034"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEREMKA"," userResponse":" KUTEREMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312608620","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312608619"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIMA"," userResponse":" MLIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312611402","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312611401"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312611896","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312611896"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312612706","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312612705"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312613977","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312613976"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKIELEKEA"," userResponse":" LIKIELEKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312614834","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312614834"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" UPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312615052","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312615051"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312615710","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312615709"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312616126","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312616126"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312616868","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312616867"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312617175","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312617174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312617988","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312617987"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASI"," userResponse":" KASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312621015","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312621014"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEREVA"," userResponse":" DEREVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312621197","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312621196"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312621733","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312621733"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312622422","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312622422"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312623806","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312623805"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIZUNGUMZA"," userResponse":" AKIZUNGUMZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312624406","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312624406"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312624902","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312624901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312625133","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312625133"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312625900","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312625899"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUNUNU"," userResponse":" RUNUNU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312628575","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312628575"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa akizingatia barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312629771","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312629770"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa akizingatia barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIZINGATIA"," userResponse":" AKIZINGATIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312630593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312630592"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa akizingatia barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312634134","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312634134"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori liligonga gari!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312635341","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312635340"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori liligonga gari!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIGONGA"," userResponse":" LILIGONGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312635683","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312635682"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori liligonga gari!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312638988","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312638988"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312639075","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312639075"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312640208","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312640208"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312641092","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312641091"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312641306","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312641305"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312642251","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312642250"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" POLISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312643707","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312643706"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFIKA"," userResponse":" WALIFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312644708","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312644708"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOA"," userResponse":" KUTOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312646140","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312646139"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USAIDIZI"," userResponse":" USAIDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312649729","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312649729"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGARI"," userResponse":" MAGARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312650598","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312650597"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWILI"," userResponse":" MAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312650703","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312650703"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312651359","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312651359"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUTA"," userResponse":" KUVUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312652220","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312652220"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGARI"," userResponse":" MAGARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312653284","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312653283"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIFIKA"," userResponse":" YALIFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312655725","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312655724"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja lilivuta lori."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312656632","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312656632"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja lilivuta lori."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIVUTA"," userResponse":" LILIVUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312657144","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312657144"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja lilivuta lori."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312659800","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312659800"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lingine likavuta gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINGINE"," userResponse":" LINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312660772","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312660771"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lingine likavuta gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAVUTA"," userResponse":" LIKAVUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312661185","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312661184"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lingine likavuta gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312664525","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312664524"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliona kila kitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIONA"," userResponse":" TULIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312664969","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312664968"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliona kila kitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312665531","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312665530"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliona kila kitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312668715","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312668714"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULITISHIKA"," userResponse":" TULITISHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312669239","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312669238"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312672099","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312672098"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312672214","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312672214"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" ac401a7b-cf81-4efe-9984-ce2d083d7044"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312682746","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312682746"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312688790","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312688790"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312689972","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312689971"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312690430","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312690430"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312693293","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312693292"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312697570","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312697569"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312699174","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312699173"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312701746","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312701746"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312703349","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312703348"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312707345","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312707345"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312708949","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312708948"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312711495","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312711494"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312713097","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312713096"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312715131","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312715130"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312716733","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312716733"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312718810","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312718810"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312720399","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312720398"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312724423","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312724422"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312725983","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312725983"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312728355","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312728354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312729982","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312729981"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312732312","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312732311"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312733918","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312733918"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312737670","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312737670"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312739267","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312739267"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312743228","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312743227"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312744852","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312744851"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312747093","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312747093"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312748694","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312748694"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312752578","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312752578"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312754165","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312754165"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312756939","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312756938"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312758545","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312758545"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312762995","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312762994"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312764598","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312764598"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312766781","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312766781"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312768362","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312768361"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312771156","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312771156"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312772765","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312772764"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312774870","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312774869"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312776426","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312776426"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312783280","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312783280"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312784882","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312784882"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312804368","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312804368"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312804512","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312804512"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312817107","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312817107"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0cd219b9-0ee5-409c-9bfb-35b58455e42d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312911050","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312911050"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" cb0a1ea7-e2dc-49fb-bf02-65eed8fff41e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312925230","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312925229"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" cb0a1ea7-e2dc-49fb-bf02-65eed8fff41e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312929087","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312929087"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" cb0a1ea7-e2dc-49fb-bf02-65eed8fff41e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312935517","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312935517"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" cb0a1ea7-e2dc-49fb-bf02-65eed8fff41e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312939092","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312939092"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" cb0a1ea7-e2dc-49fb-bf02-65eed8fff41e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312943069","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312943069"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" cb0a1ea7-e2dc-49fb-bf02-65eed8fff41e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312946534","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312946533"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" cb0a1ea7-e2dc-49fb-bf02-65eed8fff41e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-H-A"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312949781","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312949781"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" cb0a1ea7-e2dc-49fb-bf02-65eed8fff41e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312953107","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312953107"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" cb0a1ea7-e2dc-49fb-bf02-65eed8fff41e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_N-I-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312956348","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312956348"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" cb0a1ea7-e2dc-49fb-bf02-65eed8fff41e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_B-J-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312959666","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312959666"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" cb0a1ea7-e2dc-49fb-bf02-65eed8fff41e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_CH-K-D"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312966447","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312966447"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" cb0a1ea7-e2dc-49fb-bf02-65eed8fff41e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312969919","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312969919"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" cb0a1ea7-e2dc-49fb-bf02-65eed8fff41e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312972940","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312972940"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" cb0a1ea7-e2dc-49fb-bf02-65eed8fff41e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-I"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312976281","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312976280"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" cb0a1ea7-e2dc-49fb-bf02-65eed8fff41e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_R-O-E"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312980429","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312980429"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" cb0a1ea7-e2dc-49fb-bf02-65eed8fff41e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-W"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312983344","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312983344"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" cb0a1ea7-e2dc-49fb-bf02-65eed8fff41e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-E-S"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312987527","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312987527"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" cb0a1ea7-e2dc-49fb-bf02-65eed8fff41e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-L-S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312994567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312994567"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" cb0a1ea7-e2dc-49fb-bf02-65eed8fff41e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-Z-T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548312997919","data":{"timestamp":" 1548312997919"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" cb0a1ea7-e2dc-49fb-bf02-65eed8fff41e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-CH-N"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313000834","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313000834"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" cb0a1ea7-e2dc-49fb-bf02-65eed8fff41e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-A-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313004760","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313004760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" cb0a1ea7-e2dc-49fb-bf02-65eed8fff41e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-U"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313008747","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313008747"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" cb0a1ea7-e2dc-49fb-bf02-65eed8fff41e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_F-Z-Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313014301","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313014301"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" cb0a1ea7-e2dc-49fb-bf02-65eed8fff41e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_F-Z-Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313018862","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313018862"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" cb0a1ea7-e2dc-49fb-bf02-65eed8fff41e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313024625","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313024624"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" cb0a1ea7-e2dc-49fb-bf02-65eed8fff41e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313132421","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313132419"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" cb0a1ea7-e2dc-49fb-bf02-65eed8fff41e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313132541","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313132541"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 5fdb23e1-162e-4cb2-9118-ca1a7100e77f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313144677","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313144676"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313145742","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313145740"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313154317","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313154317"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313155395","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313155394"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313159005","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313159005"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313160069","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313160068"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313162728","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313162726"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313163803","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313163802"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313168825","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313168824"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313169898","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313169897"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313172678","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313172678"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313173730","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313173729"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313176534","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313176534"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313177591","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313177590"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313180681","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313180680"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313181737","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313181737"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313187676","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313187675"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313188750","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313188750"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313191597","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313191597"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313192662","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313192661"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313195237","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313195236"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313196303","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313196302"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313203503","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313203502"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313204570","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313204570"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313209601","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313209601"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313210674","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313210674"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313213632","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313213632"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313214676","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313214675"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313218421","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313218421"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313219472","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313219472"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313222384","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313222384"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313223454","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313223452"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313227100","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313227100"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313228176","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313228175"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313231492","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313231492"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313232538","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313232537"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313235344","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313235343"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313236407","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313236407"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313240428","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313240428"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313241469","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313241467"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313244175","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313244175"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313245235","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313245234"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313247831","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313247830"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313248898","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313248897"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313255257","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313255257"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313256300","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313256300"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313259145","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313259145"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313260204","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313260204"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313263579","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313263578"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548313263698","data":{"timestamp":" 1548313263698"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" bad3a197-9e1a-4d73-b849-50decfb4eaf3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314533601","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314533601"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 7690b7a5-f589-4454-8754-92c9e7665bb5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_0-1-10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314552251","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314552251"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 7690b7a5-f589-4454-8754-92c9e7665bb5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_0-1-10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314574878","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314574878"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 7690b7a5-f589-4454-8754-92c9e7665bb5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_9-11-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314593215","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314593215"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 7690b7a5-f589-4454-8754-92c9e7665bb5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-3-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314600770","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314600770"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 7690b7a5-f589-4454-8754-92c9e7665bb5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-3-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314606569","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314606569"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 7690b7a5-f589-4454-8754-92c9e7665bb5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-3-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314626005","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314626005"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 7690b7a5-f589-4454-8754-92c9e7665bb5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_1-13-6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314643722","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314643721"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 7690b7a5-f589-4454-8754-92c9e7665bb5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_4-13-6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314653596","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314653596"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 7690b7a5-f589-4454-8754-92c9e7665bb5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_4-12-13"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 13"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314660134","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314660134"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 7690b7a5-f589-4454-8754-92c9e7665bb5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_4-12-13"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314665894","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314665893"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 7690b7a5-f589-4454-8754-92c9e7665bb5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-13"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314670283","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314670283"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 7690b7a5-f589-4454-8754-92c9e7665bb5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_15_9-10-15"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 15"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314676092","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314676092"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 7690b7a5-f589-4454-8754-92c9e7665bb5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_15_9-10-15"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 15"," userResponse":" 15"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314761652","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314761652"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 7690b7a5-f589-4454-8754-92c9e7665bb5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_1-4-7"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314767517","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314767517"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 7690b7a5-f589-4454-8754-92c9e7665bb5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314773612","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314773611"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 7690b7a5-f589-4454-8754-92c9e7665bb5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314780234","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314780232"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 7690b7a5-f589-4454-8754-92c9e7665bb5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_6_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314788981","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314788981"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" a2cd42ed-2b50-4660-b5eb-b5e0dd5d85cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314793215","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314793215"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" a2cd42ed-2b50-4660-b5eb-b5e0dd5d85cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314798429","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314798429"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" a2cd42ed-2b50-4660-b5eb-b5e0dd5d85cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314802766","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314802766"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" a2cd42ed-2b50-4660-b5eb-b5e0dd5d85cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314807636","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314807636"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" a2cd42ed-2b50-4660-b5eb-b5e0dd5d85cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314811171","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314811170"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" a2cd42ed-2b50-4660-b5eb-b5e0dd5d85cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314815312","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314815311"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" a2cd42ed-2b50-4660-b5eb-b5e0dd5d85cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314819033","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314819033"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" a2cd42ed-2b50-4660-b5eb-b5e0dd5d85cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314822738","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314822737"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" a2cd42ed-2b50-4660-b5eb-b5e0dd5d85cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314826272","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314826272"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" a2cd42ed-2b50-4660-b5eb-b5e0dd5d85cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-I-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314830045","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314830045"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" a2cd42ed-2b50-4660-b5eb-b5e0dd5d85cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_T-I-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314836518","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314836518"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" a2cd42ed-2b50-4660-b5eb-b5e0dd5d85cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_B-R-K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314854494","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314854494"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" a2cd42ed-2b50-4660-b5eb-b5e0dd5d85cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314858336","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314858336"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" a2cd42ed-2b50-4660-b5eb-b5e0dd5d85cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-W-N"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314862230","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314862230"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" a2cd42ed-2b50-4660-b5eb-b5e0dd5d85cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314867564","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314867564"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" a2cd42ed-2b50-4660-b5eb-b5e0dd5d85cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314870660","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314870660"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" a2cd42ed-2b50-4660-b5eb-b5e0dd5d85cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-D-R"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314874613","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314874613"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" a2cd42ed-2b50-4660-b5eb-b5e0dd5d85cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-P-B"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314878087","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314878087"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" a2cd42ed-2b50-4660-b5eb-b5e0dd5d85cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_e-S-n"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314882461","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314882461"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" a2cd42ed-2b50-4660-b5eb-b5e0dd5d85cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-J-F"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314885891","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314885891"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" a2cd42ed-2b50-4660-b5eb-b5e0dd5d85cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314889271","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314889270"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" a2cd42ed-2b50-4660-b5eb-b5e0dd5d85cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-U-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314893001","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314893000"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" a2cd42ed-2b50-4660-b5eb-b5e0dd5d85cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314896311","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314896311"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" a2cd42ed-2b50-4660-b5eb-b5e0dd5d85cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314899477","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314899477"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" a2cd42ed-2b50-4660-b5eb-b5e0dd5d85cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548314905216","data":{"timestamp":" 1548314905214"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" a2cd42ed-2b50-4660-b5eb-b5e0dd5d85cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315100212","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315100211"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" a2cd42ed-2b50-4660-b5eb-b5e0dd5d85cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315100286","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315100286"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 62d7ffa5-6965-4bf4-aafe-270dcd9a3a45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315121453","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315121453"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 62d7ffa5-6965-4bf4-aafe-270dcd9a3a45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315121520","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315121520"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 8d6bc67c-baac-4d9a-96c8-8704ab098882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315129359","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315129359"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 45697fd0-a223-453e-aa5b-85cf4f3efd4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_I-U-G"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315132901","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315132901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 45697fd0-a223-453e-aa5b-85cf4f3efd4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_O-E-G"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315138363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315138363"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 45697fd0-a223-453e-aa5b-85cf4f3efd4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_G_O-E-G"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315148376","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315148376"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" edc94a4c-a47b-42e6-87fe-23ea4beceeb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_1-4-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315156812","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315156812"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" edc94a4c-a47b-42e6-87fe-23ea4beceeb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_4-13-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315194570","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315194570"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" edc94a4c-a47b-42e6-87fe-23ea4beceeb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_15_9-10-15"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 15"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315200602","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315200602"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" edc94a4c-a47b-42e6-87fe-23ea4beceeb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_15_9-10-15"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 15"," userResponse":" 15"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315206397","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315206397"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" edc94a4c-a47b-42e6-87fe-23ea4beceeb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-13"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315210684","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315210684"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" edc94a4c-a47b-42e6-87fe-23ea4beceeb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_4-12-13"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315216256","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315216256"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" edc94a4c-a47b-42e6-87fe-23ea4beceeb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315234443","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315234443"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" edc94a4c-a47b-42e6-87fe-23ea4beceeb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-3-4"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315246531","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315246531"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" edc94a4c-a47b-42e6-87fe-23ea4beceeb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_1-13-6"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315253717","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315253717"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" edc94a4c-a47b-42e6-87fe-23ea4beceeb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_0-1-10"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315265351","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315265351"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" edc94a4c-a47b-42e6-87fe-23ea4beceeb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_9-11-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315271779","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315271779"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" edc94a4c-a47b-42e6-87fe-23ea4beceeb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_9-11-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315278384","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315278383"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" edc94a4c-a47b-42e6-87fe-23ea4beceeb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_6_9-11-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315286897","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315286897"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 6731d2bf-e879-4243-96f3-6d4590b7d872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_I-F-G"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315290029","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315290029"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 6731d2bf-e879-4243-96f3-6d4590b7d872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-O-F"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315293503","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315293503"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 6731d2bf-e879-4243-96f3-6d4590b7d872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_Y-G-O"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315296883","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315296883"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 6731d2bf-e879-4243-96f3-6d4590b7d872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_CH-G-Y"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315299937","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315299937"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 6731d2bf-e879-4243-96f3-6d4590b7d872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_J-G-P"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315303368","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315303368"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 6731d2bf-e879-4243-96f3-6d4590b7d872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_D-G-I"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315307040","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315307039"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 6731d2bf-e879-4243-96f3-6d4590b7d872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_E-Y-G"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315310428","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315310428"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 6731d2bf-e879-4243-96f3-6d4590b7d872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_T-Z-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315313671","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315313670"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 6731d2bf-e879-4243-96f3-6d4590b7d872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_I-G-P"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315329394","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315329394"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 6731d2bf-e879-4243-96f3-6d4590b7d872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_B-M-G"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315334575","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315334575"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 6731d2bf-e879-4243-96f3-6d4590b7d872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_B-M-G"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315340310","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315340308"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 6731d2bf-e879-4243-96f3-6d4590b7d872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_G_B-M-G"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315372989","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315372989"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 7eeac197-7bf2-407d-8cb0-31ac415f4e49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315393022","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315393022"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 7eeac197-7bf2-407d-8cb0-31ac415f4e49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315411249","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315411249"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 7eeac197-7bf2-407d-8cb0-31ac415f4e49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315431608","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315431607"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 7eeac197-7bf2-407d-8cb0-31ac415f4e49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315459087","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315459086"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 7eeac197-7bf2-407d-8cb0-31ac415f4e49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315459208","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315459208"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 7eeac197-7bf2-407d-8cb0-31ac415f4e49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315465857","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315465856"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 7eeac197-7bf2-407d-8cb0-31ac415f4e49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315472463","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315472463"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 7eeac197-7bf2-407d-8cb0-31ac415f4e49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315481748","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315481748"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315484876","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315484876"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315488683","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315488683"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315492602","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315492601"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315496495","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315496495"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315503708","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315503708"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315507919","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315507919"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-H-A"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315529594","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315529594"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315533009","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315533009"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_N-I-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315536543","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315536543"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_B-J-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315541739","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315541739"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_CH-K-D"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315546029","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315546029"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315552067","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315552067"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315557906","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315557906"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315566176","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315566175"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-I"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315572057","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315572057"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-I"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315576095","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315576095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_R-O-E"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315579784","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315579784"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-W"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315591888","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315591888"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-E-S"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315597172","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315597172"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-L-S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315600903","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315600903"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-Z-T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315604028","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315604028"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-CH-N"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315607071","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315607071"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-A-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315612459","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315612459"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-A-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315618881","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315618881"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-U"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315626276","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315626276"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_F-Z-Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315634688","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315634688"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_F-Z-Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315638599","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315638599"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315644346","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315644346"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315650092","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315650092"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 0c4888b9-1022-4176-a1ce-dba33437599f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315682354","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315682354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 13dc4f98-90e6-4337-b29d-265568034792"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315684871","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315684870"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 13dc4f98-90e6-4337-b29d-265568034792"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315715123","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315715123"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 13dc4f98-90e6-4337-b29d-265568034792"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315738395","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315738394"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 13dc4f98-90e6-4337-b29d-265568034792"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315765794","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315765793"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 13dc4f98-90e6-4337-b29d-265568034792"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315765909","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315765908"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 13dc4f98-90e6-4337-b29d-265568034792"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315774082","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315774081"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 13dc4f98-90e6-4337-b29d-265568034792"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..22.off2.17__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315779705","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315779705"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" 13dc4f98-90e6-4337-b29d-265568034792"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315788681","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315788681"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315791837","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315791837"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315795585","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315795585"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315798998","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315798997"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315803262","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315803262"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315806624","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315806624"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315810757","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315810757"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315815020","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315815020"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315818656","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315818656"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-I-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315822243","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315822243"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_T-I-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315825687","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315825687"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_B-R-K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315828606","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315828606"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315835037","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315835037"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315839231","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315839231"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-W-N"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315845979","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315845979"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-W-N"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315851605","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315851605"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-W-N"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315859573","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315859573"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315865422","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315865422"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315872971","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315872971"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-D-R"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315877132","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315877132"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-P-B"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315882955","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315882955"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_e-S-n"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315888431","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315888431"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-J-F"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315892822","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315892822"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315897676","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315897676"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-U-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315904230","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315904230"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315910611","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315910611"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315915656","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315915656"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315921450","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315921450"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_094752"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}